# September 202

# **GABE** MARROQUIN

# DESIGNER/ARTIST

gabemarroquin.art@gmail.com gabeee.co @the.gabe.marroquin 845.549.8568

### **PROFILE**

Hi! I'm a designer and self-taught artist dedicated to creating and inspiring through innovative and thoughtful visual works.

With my unique blend of design expertise and artistic intuition, I strive to craft narrative works that not only capture attention but also evoke emotions and provoke thought.

# **SKILLS**

Microsoft Office 365
Adobe InDesign
Adobe Illustrator
Adobe After Effects
Adobe Photoshop
HTML/CSS Knowledge
Web Design & Layout
Figma
UX/UI
Wireframing & Prototyping
Motion Graphics
Illustration
Drawing

#### **LANGUAGES**

English Spanish

Digital Art

### **EXPERIENCE**

# **GRAPHIC DESIGN INTERN**

JACKFIR (June 2024-September 2024)

Assist in marketing and UX by developing cohesive email designs, digital ads, and product pages that align with the brand's visual identity.

# **COORDINATOR & STUDIO TECH**

92NY Art Center (2023 - Current)

Provide administrative and technical support to manage daily logistics of the Art Center. Oversee art studio facilities, supplies, and equipment to ensure safety and compliance with protocols. Collaborate with instructors to ensure smooth class operations and act as the senior point of contact for faculty and student support during weekend programs.

#### **TEACHING ASSISTANT**

92NY Art Center (2022 - Current/Seasonal)

Work alongside art instructors to set up classrooms and prepare materials for after-school lessons. Occasionally substitute in other classes and lead instruction towards the end of the semester.

# **EDUCATION**

#### PARSON SCHOOL OF DESIGN

2023 - Current

AAS Communication Design

# **NYACK COLLEGE**

2020

Intercultural Studies BA

# CREATIVE DEVELOPMENT

# **92NY**

2022-2023

Digital Drawing & Painting Watercolor painting Drawing Ceramics